betterproposals.io 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy - Better Proposals

### Legal Definition

### What this means in English

1\. WHO WE ARE

Put simply, Advantix Technologies Ltd ("Better Proposals", "us" or "we") provides a simple proposal creation tool. Our registered company number is 08961263, and our registered address is Palladium House, 1-4 Argyll Street, London, W1F 7LD

Some basic details about who we are. 

2\. WHO AND WHAT THIS POLICY APPLIES TO

2.1 Our Privacy Policy deals with how we handle “personal information” as it is defined in the Privacy Act (Personal Information).

2.2 We handle Personal Information for our own business, as well as potentially storing Personal Information in our systems on behalf of our customers and users that input Personal Information into our systems.

2.3 Our Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect about businesses or companies, however it does apply to information about the people in those businesses or companies which we store.

2.4 The Privacy Policy applies to all forms of information, physical and digital, whether collected or stored electronically or in hardcopy.

2.5 Our website and services are unavailable to children (persons under the age of 18 years). If an individual is under 18 years of age, they can only use our website and services under the supervision of a parent or guardian.

This Privacy Policy applies to any information collected and/or stored about our customers and users, and any information they provide about others. 

3\. THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

3.1 In the course of business it is necessary for us to collect Personal Information. This information allows us to identify who an individual is for the purposes of our business, share Personal Information when asked of us, contact the individual in the ordinary course of business and transact with the individual. Without limitation, the type of information we may collect is:

(a) Personal Information. We may collect personal details such as an individual’s name, location, date of birth, nationality, family details and other information defined as “Personal Information” in the Privacy Act that allows us to identify who the individual is;  
(b) Contact Information. We may collect information such as an individual’s email address, telephone & fax number, third-party usernames, residential, business and postal address and other information that allows us to contact the individual;  
(c) Financial Information. We may collect financial information related to an individual such as any bank or credit card details used to transact with us and other information that allows us to transact with the individual and/or provide them with our services;  
(d) Statistical Information. We may collect information about an individual’s online and offline preferences, habits, movements, trends, decisions, associations, memberships, finances, purchases and other information for statistical purposes; and Information an individual sends us. We may collect any personal correspondence that an individual sends us, or that is sent to us by others about the individual’s activities.

3.2 We may collect other Personal Information about an individual, which we will maintain in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

3.3 We may also collect non-Personal Information about an individual such as information regarding their computer, network and browser. This may include their IP address. Where non-Personal Information is collected the UK Privacy Principles do not apply. 

3.4 Any time an individual provides Personal Information or other information about someone other than himself or herself, the individual warrants that they have that person's consent to provide such information for the purpose specified. 

1\. We may collect or request various types of information for standard business usage such as support and marketing purposes. 

2\. We may also collect non-Personal information such as which browser you are using for example. 

3\. When you provide someone else's information, you have to have their consent first. 

4\. HOW INFORMATION IS COLLECTED

4.1 Most information will be collected in association with an individual’s use of Better Proposals, an enquiry about Better Proposals, or generally dealing with us. However we may also receive Personal Information from sources such as advertising, an individual’s own promotions, public records, mailing lists, contractors, staff, recruitment agencies and our business partners. In particular, information is likely to be collected as follows:

(a) Registrations/Subscriptions. When an individual registers or subscribes for a service, list, account, connection or other process whereby they enter Personal Information details in order to receive or access something, including a transaction;  
(b) Accounts/Memberships.  
When an individual submits their details to open an account and/or become a member with us;  
(c) Supply. When an individual supplies us with goods or services;  
(d) Contact. When an individual contacts us in any way;  
(e) Access. When an individual accesses us physically we may require them to provide us with details for us to permit them such access. When an individual accesses us through the internet we may collect information using cookies (if relevant – an individual can adjust their browser’s setting to accept or reject cookies) or analytical services; and/or Pixel Tags. Pixel tags enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read and they tell us whether mail has been opened.

4.2 As there are many circumstances in which we may collect information both electronically and physically, we will endeavour to ensure that an individual is always aware of when their Personal Information is being collected.

4.3 Where we obtain Personal Information without an individual’s knowledge (such as by accidental acquisition from a client) we will either delete/destroy the information, or inform the individual that we hold such information, in accordance with the UK Privacy Principles. 

Information will primarily be collected through usage of the system, sometimes explicitly asked for, other times by way of analytics software. 

5\. WHEN PERSONAL INFORMATION IS USED & DISCLOSED

5.1 In general, the primary principle is that we will not use any Personal Information other than for the purpose for which it was collected other than with the individual’s permission. The purpose of collection is determined by the circumstances in which the information was collected and/or submitted.

5.2 We will retain Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfil the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

5.3 It may be necessary for us to disclose an individual’s Personal Information to third parties in a manner compliant with the UK Privacy Principles in the course of our business.

5.4 We will not disclose or sell an individual’s Personal Information to unrelated third parties under any circumstances.

5.5 Information is used to enable us to operate our business, especially as it relates to an individual. This may include: The provision of goods and services between an individual and us; Verifying an individual’s identity; Communicating with an individual about: Their relationship with us; Our goods and services; Our own marketing and promotions to customers and prospects; Competitions, surveys and questionnaires; Investigating any complaints about or made by an individual, or if we have reason to suspect that an individual is in breach of any of our terms and conditions or that an individual is or has been otherwise engaged in any unlawful activity; and/or As required or permitted by any law (including the Privacy Act).

5.6 There are some circumstances in which we must disclose an individual’s information: Where we reasonably believe that an individual may be engaged in fraudulent, deceptive or unlawful activity that a governmental authority should be made aware of; As required by any law (including the Privacy Act); and/or In order to sell our business (in that we may need to transfer Personal Information to a new owner).

5.7 We will not disclose an individual’s Personal Information to any entity outside of the UK that is in a jurisdiction that does not have a similar regime to the UK Privacy Principles or an implemented and enforceable privacy policy similar to this Privacy Policy. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that any disclosure to an entity outside of the UK will not be made until that entity has agreed in writing with us to safeguard Personal Information as we do.

5.8 We may utilise third-pay service providers (such as SendGrid from SendGrid, Inc., and Intercom from Intercom, Inc.) to communicate with an individual and to store contact details about an individual. These service providers are located in the United States of America.

5.9 All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services providers, Stripe and GoCardless. You can review their respective privacy policies at https://stripe.com/privacy and https://gocardless.com/legal/privacy. We will share information with our payment services providers only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds. 

1\. Generally your information will only be use in conjunction with your usage of the system. 

2\. We may allow information to be passed to related software such as analytics systems for the purpose of our own records, communication with you and marketing. 

3\. We will never sell your data to a third party. 

4\. If we believe you are doing anything fraudulent or illegal, we reserve the right to share your information with the necessary authorities. 

6\. OPTING “IN” OR “OUT”

6.1 An individual may opt to not have us collect their Personal Information. This may prevent us from offering them some or all of our services and may terminate their access to some or all of the services they access with or through us. They will be aware of this when: Opt In. Where relevant, the individual will have the right to choose to have information collected and/or receive information from us; or Opt Out. Where relevant, the individual will have the right to choose to exclude himself or herself from some or all collection of information and/or receiving information from us.

6.2 If an individual believes that they have received information from us that they did not opt in or out to receive, they should contact us on the details below.

You can unsubscribe from any of our marketing activity by using the built-in unsubscribe link or getting in touch with us directly. 

7\. THE SAFETY & SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

7.1 We may appoint a Privacy Officer to oversee the management of this Privacy Policy and compliance with the UK Privacy Principles and the Privacy Act. This officer may have other duties within our business and also be assisted by internal and external professionals and advisors.

7.2 We will take all reasonable precautions to protect an individual’s Personal Information from unauthorised access. This includes appropriately securing our physical facilities and electronic networks.

7.3 The security of online transactions and the security of communications sent by electronic means or by post cannot be guaranteed. Each individual that provides information to us via the internet or by post does so at their own risk. We cannot accept responsibility for misuse or loss of, or unauthorised access to, Personal Information where the security of information is not within our control.

7.4 We are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of any third party (including third parties that we are permitted to disclose an individual’s Personal Information to in accordance with this policy or any applicable laws). The collection and use of an individual’s information by such third parties may be subject to separate privacy and security policies.

7.5 If an individual suspects any misuse or loss of, or unauthorised access to, their Personal Information, they should let us know immediately.

7.6 We are not liable for any loss, damage or claim arising out of another person’s use of the Personal Information where we were authorised to provide that person with the Personal Information.

1\. We will take every measure to keep your personal information protected, by ensuring the security of our servers and site. 

2\. The internet is a big place. When the security of an online transaction isn't under our control, we'll do everything on our end to ensure you're protected and the rest is outside the scope of this policy. 

8\. HOW TO ACCESS AND/OR UPDATE INFORMATION

8.1 Subject to the UK Privacy Principles, an individual has the right to request from us the Personal Information that we have about them, and we have an obligation to provide them with such information within 28 days of receiving their written request.

8.2 An individual has the right to request the removal of any and all Personal Information that we have about them, and we have an obligation to remove such information within 28 days of receiving their written request.

8.3 If an individual cannot update his or her own information, we will correct any errors in the Personal Information we hold about an individual within 7 days of receiving written notice from them about those errors.

8.4 It is an individual’s responsibility to provide us with accurate and truthful Personal Information. We cannot be liable for any information that is provided to us that is incorrect.

8.5 We may charge an individual a reasonable fee for our costs incurred in meeting any of their requests to disclose the Personal Information we hold about them.

1\. You can request that we send you any personal information we hold about you. 

2\. You can request that we remove any personal information we hold about you. 

3\. We will allow you to update your information or action this for you in cases where it's not possible to do so yourself. 

4\. Any information you provide is assumed as true, we're not responsible if your name is entered incorrectly for example. 

9\. COMPLAINTS AND DISPUTES

9.1 If an individual has a complaint about our handling of their Personal Information, they should address their complaint in writing to the details below.

9.2 If we have a dispute regarding an individual’s Personal Information, we both must first attempt to resolve the issue directly between us.

9.3 If we become aware of any unauthorised access to an individual’s Personal Information we will inform them at the earliest practical opportunity once we have established what was accessed and how it was accessed.

1\. You can get in touch with us directly if you have any concerns over the personal information we hold. 

2\. If we become aware of any compromise to your information, we'll let you know as soon as possible. 

10\. CONTACTING INDIVIDUALS

10.1 From time to time, we may send an individual important notices, such as changes to our terms, conditions and policies. Because this information is important to the individual’s interaction with us, they may not opt out of receiving these communications.

You can't unsubscribe from certain emails that update you about legal information such as updates to our terms. 

11\. CONTACTING US

11.1 All correspondence with regards to privacy should be addressed to: The Privacy Officer, Better Proposals, Palladium House, 1-4 Argyll Street, London W1F 7LD or email support@betterproposals.io. You may contact the Privacy Officer by email in the first instance.

12\. ADDITIONS TO THIS POLICY

12.1 If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on our webpage at www.betterproposals.io. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy to review any amendments.

12.2 We may do things in addition to what is stated in this Privacy Policy to comply with the UK Privacy Principles, and nothing in this Privacy Policy shall deem us to have not complied with the UK Privacy Principles.
